7 directors. 7 tales of terror.  0 working cell phones.
Scare Package is a horror, comedy film directed by Courtney Andujar.
Chad Buckley is super crazy about horror movies, but also very lonely.
He mostly spends his days in his small movie shop having wild
discussions with his only returning customer, Sam.
Chad Buckley, played by Jeremy King.
Sam, played by Byron Brown.
Hawn, played by Hawn Tran.
Mike Myers, played by Jon Michael Simpson.
Jessie, played by Zoe Graham.
Husband, played by Noah Segan.
Scare Package is a 2019 American anthology horror
comedy film created by Aaron B.
Koontz and Cameron Burns.
It features a series of horror shorts written and directed by Aaron B.
Koontz, Courtney Andujar, Hillary Andujar, Anthony Cousins, Emily
Hagins, Chris McInroy, Noah Segan, and Baron Vaughn.
The film debuted at the Sitges Film Festival in October 2019, and
was released exclusively on Shudder on June 18, 2020.
A sequel to the film was announced in late 2021.
Scare Package II: Rad Chad's Revenge was released on Shudder December 2022.
The film explores themes of anthology, horror spoof, horror anthology.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.